{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "21st Century",
    "Term": "First Quarter",
    "Title": "Week-1",
    "LastModified": "14 August 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "Week-1"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "What came from the Latin word 'literatura' which means 'writing formed with letters'?",
      "answer": "Literature",
      "choices": [
        "Fiction",
        "Non-Fiction",
        "Literature",
        "Prose"
      ],
      "reference": "21ST-REVIEWER-WEEK1.docx.pdf",
      "term": "Literature Basics"
    },
    {
      "question": "What refers to artistic writings worthy of being remembered?",
      "answer": "Literature",
      "choices": [
        "Prose",
        "Fiction",
        "Literature",
        "Non-Fiction"
      ],
      "reference": "21ST-REVIEWER-WEEK1.docx.pdf",
      "term": "Literature Basics"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is it where the authors make up the entire story, they can choose to include information in a made-up story?",
      "answer": "Fiction",
      "choices": [
        "Non-Fiction",
        "Prose",
        "Fiction",
        "Literature"
      ],
      "reference": "21ST-REVIEWER-WEEK1.docx.pdf",
      "term": "Branches of Literature"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is also called 'informational materials', this type of literature provides information that is factual?",
      "answer": "Non-Fiction",
      "choices": [
        "Fiction",
        "Non-Fiction",
        "Prose",
        "Literature"
      ],
      "reference": "21ST-REVIEWER-WEEK1.docx.pdf",
      "term": "Branches of Literature"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a form of language which implies ordinary grammatical structure and natural flow of speech rather than rhythmic structure?",
      "answer": "Prose",
      "choices": [
        "Literature",
        "Non-Fiction",
        "Fiction",
        "Prose"
      ],
      "reference": "21ST-REVIEWER-WEEK1.docx.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Literature"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a fictitious prose narrative of book length, typically representing character and action with some degree of realism?",
      "answer": "Novel",
      "choices": [
        "Short Story",
        "Play",
        "Novel",
        "Essay"
      ],
      "reference": "21ST-REVIEWER-WEEK1.docx.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Prose"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a story with a fully developed theme but significantly shorter and less elaborate than a novel?",
      "answer": "Short Story",
      "choices": [
        "Novel",
        "Short Story",
        "Play",
        "Legend"
      ],
      "reference": "21ST-REVIEWER-WEEK1.docx.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Prose"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a work of drama, usually consisting mostly of dialogue between characters and intended for theatrical performance rather than just reading?",
      "answer": "Plays",
      "choices": [
        "Novel",
        "Fable",
        "Plays",
        "Short Story"
      ],
      "reference": "21ST-REVIEWER-WEEK1.docx.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Prose"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a short piece of writing on a particular subject?",
      "answer": "Essay",
      "choices": [
        "Essay",
        "Biography",
        "Anecdote",
        "Myth"
      ],
      "reference": "21ST-REVIEWER-WEEK1.docx.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Prose"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a traditional story sometimes popularly regarded as historical but unauthenticated?",
      "answer": "Legends",
      "choices": [
        "Fables",
        "Myth",
        "Legends",
        "Anecdotes"
      ],
      "reference": "21ST-REVIEWER-WEEK1.docx.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Prose"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a short story, typically with animals as characters, conveying a moral?",
      "answer": "Fables",
      "choices": [
        "Legends",
        "Fables",
        "Myth",
        "Anecdotes"
      ],
      "reference": "21ST-REVIEWER-WEEK1.docx.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Prose"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a short amusing or interesting story about a real incident or person?",
      "answer": "Anecdotes",
      "choices": [
        "Myth",
        "Fables",
        "Legends",
        "Anecdotes"
      ],
      "reference": "21ST-REVIEWER-WEEK1.docx.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Prose"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a traditional story, especially one concerning the early history of a people or explaining some natural or social phenomenon and typically involving supernatural beings or events?",
      "answer": "Myth",
      "choices": [
        "Myth",
        "Fables",
        "Legends",
        "Anecdotes"
      ],
      "reference": "21ST-REVIEWER-WEEK1.docx.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Prose"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an account of someone's life written by someone else?",
      "answer": "Biography",
      "choices": [
        "News",
        "Essay",
        "Biography",
        "Novel"
      ],
      "reference": "21ST-REVIEWER-WEEK1.docx.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Prose"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is newly received or noteworthy information, especially about recent or important events?",
      "answer": "News",
      "choices": [
        "Biography",
        "Essay",
        "News",
        "Short Story"
      ],
      "reference": "21ST-REVIEWER-WEEK1.docx.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Prose"
    }
  ]
}